hi and welcome to living in Central
Texas today I'll be showing you this
stunning semi-custom new construction
home in Temple Texas this home is
located off of fm93 and 31st Street in
the community of Valor Estates my
clients move in in 3 days they are so
excited but first I wanted to show you
how it all came together now make sure
to watch all the way through so that you
can see the custom dog shower and the
Magnificent luxury kitchen let's take a
look this is a beautiful Mediterranean
inspired custom home built by Walmart
construction when my client reached out
to me she stated that the outside of the
home really needed to look a particular
way sending me lots of pictures for
inspiration she wanted a dream kitchen
and said that that was actually the most
important feature to her in the home and
she also wanted a dog shower for her
golden retriever after getting an idea
of all of her once her current situation
and financial options I went ahead and
set up a meeting with three fantastic
local builders that I knew she would
love I wanted to make sure that she
really connected with the builder that
would be building her forever home I
wasn't surprised when she elected to go
with Glenn at Walmart construction and
could really see their personalities
clicking from the start the entire build
process was done from FaceTime and
virtual virtual selections and phone
conversations so there was a lot of
trust that went into this build and
honestly I think my client was beyond
excited about her home this home is in a
super quiet culde
saac the front of the home is super
elegant very clean and bright with a
beautiful off-white stucco and white
Austin limestone
[Music]
okay but seriously check out this
kitchen when my client was building this
custom home her biggest priority was a
kitchen that she would fall in love with
and we really nailed it all of her
selections were perfect she picked these
wonderful and beautiful quartz
countertops with gray vein
black accents throughout so you have
your black pendant lights black Hardware
it really is wonderful this floor plan
allowed for a huge
kitchen so from the kitchen you have
your living space which all flows nicely
into the formal dining space beautiful
chandelier to go over the table she has
an accent wall again the blue matches
the blue over the kitchen island and
these awesome trimmed picture windows to
put big either pictures mirrors that's
going to look really great in there this
is a super open concept floor plan this
is a floor plan that the Builder has
done in the past that he allowed the
buyer to make modifications to
[Music]
yes you're seeing this right this
spoiled golden retriever has her own dog
shower in the laundry room with her own
accented flooring
[Music]
it's a three bed three bath home with a
movie room or a theater room flex room
whatever you would like to call it which
could actually be repurposed as a fourth
bedroom if desired
[Music]
the backyard is huge as you can tell I
think the Builder said there were over
60 palettes of sod so much space for her
sweet dog
Chanel a nice little touch is this
outdoor kitchen area
[Music]
thank you so much for touring my
client's beautiful custombuilt home here
in Temple Texas if you're interested in
building your own custom home you can
find all my contact information below
let's book a call and discuss what
dreams you have in your own custom build
till next time
[Music]